Guide to the Sarah Hoskins photographs, 2000-2014 RL.10153
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sarah Hoskins photographs
2000-2014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Hoskins, Sarah
Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
RL.10153
3.0 Linear Feet 5 flat boxes
10.3 Gigabytes 10.3 GB transferred from external hard drive.
Collection contain images related to two photography projects by Sarah Hoskins. The Homeplace series contains 250 11x14 inch silver gelatin prints documenting Hoskins' visits and relationships with rural African American communities in Kentucky, originally established by freedmen in the 19th century. Her photographs include community events and activities such as hog butchering, church services, family reunions, and gatherings of charity groups. The Rosenwald Schools series contains approximately 300 color digital images of schools for African Americans built during the first half of the 20th century through the Rosenwald foundation, as well as some portraits of former students in Kentucky, North Carolina and Alabama. The series also includes images of a Rosenwald foundation-funded apartment building in Chicago, Illinois. Acquired by the Archive of Documentary Arts.
Collection Overview
Collection contain images related to two photography projects by Sarah Hoskins: The Rosenwald Schools and The Homeplace.
The Homeplace series contains 250 11x14 inch silver gelatin black-and-white prints documenting Hoskins' visits and relationships with rural African American communities in Kentucky, originally established by freedmen in the 19th century. Her photographs include community events and activities such as hog butchering, church services, family reunions, and gatherings of charity groups.
The Rosenwald Schools series contains approximately 300 color digital images of schools for African Americans built during the first half of the 20th century through the Rosenwald foundation, as well as portraits of some former students in Kentucky, North Carolina and Alabama. The series also includes images of a Rosenwald foundation-funded apartment building in Chicago, Illinois.
Acquired by the Archive of Documentary Arts.
Biographical Note
Sarah Hoskins is a Midwest-based documentary photographer; currently her time is split between Chicago and Lexington.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Sarah Hoskins photographs were acquired as a purchase by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 2014-2015.
African Americans -- Photographs; African Americans -- Education -- Southern States; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses -- Kentucky; African American churches -- Kentucky; Tobacco farmers -- Kentucky; Family reunions -- Kentucky; Documentary Photography -- Kentucky; African Americans -- Kentucky -- Social life and customs; Communities -- Kentucky; Family reunions -- Kentucky; Documentary Photography -- Kentucky; African American churches -- North Carolina; Communities -- North Carolina; Documentary Photography -- North Carolina; Documentary Photography -- Illinois -- Chicago; Documentary Photography -- Alabama -- Montgomery County; Race discrimination; Gelatin silver prints; Color photographs; Digital images; Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Julius Rosenwald Fund -- Buildings -- Kentucky -- North Carolina -- Pictorial works -- Chicago, Illinois -- Alabama
- The Homeplace, 2000-2014; 1; 3.0 Linear Feet (250) 11x14" Silver Gelatin Prints in 5 flat boxes.
  Scope and Contents
  The Homeplace documents the traditions and daily lives of African American communities in Kentucky's Inner Bluegrass region that were originally founded by freed slaves following the Civil War. As Hoskins states:
  "Today many of the residents are descendants of the freed men and women who founded these hamlets. In some cases as many as six generations of a family have lived in succession on a "homeplace" in these communities. Some of these hamlets are prospering while the exisitence of others is tenuous."
  The Homeplace documents events such as hog butchering; harvesting and drying tobacco; worship services at community churches; service group meetings, such as the Union Benevolent Society Lodge; creekside baptisms; and family reunions, meals, and gatherings. Each print has been assigned an RL ID and includes Hoskins' original title and caption.
  - Tub and Table, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0001)
    The barn where the hog killing is to take place. Empty tub and table. "There has to be frost on the ground." Ernest Talbert tells me in order to kill hogs. New Zion, KY.
  - Buckets and Hooks, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0002)
    The barn before the hog killing begins. New Zion, KY.
  - The Group, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0003)
    L-R Derek Talbert, Ernest Talbert, Regind Happy, Leroy Talbert, Gary Talbert, Bobby "RJ" Hayes, Rodney Talbert, Amos Coma. New Zion, KY.
  - Hog and Gun, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0004)
    Leroy Talbert has just fired the shot, Gary Talbert on left, Rodney on right. New Zion, KY.
  - Holding Back, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0005)
    The hog had been shot, but had not died yet. Leroy was tring to quicken the process using a knife. RJ Hayes and Regind Happy hold the hog back as Rodney Talbert leans in. New Zion, KY.
  - Rinsing Away, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0006)
    Leroy Talbert, Regind Happy, and Gary Talbert rinse off the hogs before they come out of the shoot into the tub of hot lye. New Zion, KY.
  - Hog Out of Shoot, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0007)
    L-R Leroy Talbert, Amos Coma and Rodney Talbert pull the hog out of shoot and are about to put hog in tub. New Zion, KY.
  - Tub of Lye, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0008)
    L-R Regind Happy, Leroy Talbert, Gary Talbert, Rodney Talbert and Amos Coma work the hog in tub of Lye. New Zion, KY.
  - Hog In Tub, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0009)
    Leroy, Gary, and Rodney Talbert push the hog down in the scalding tub of Lye. I met Leroy and most of the others for the first time that night. Leroy glared at me and said, "we're here to work." He is my dear, dear friend now. We laugh as it could have gone the other way had I fallen from the slick table I was standing on. New Zion, KY.
  - Hog Out of Tub, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0010)
    L-R Gary, Rodney Talbert, Amos Coma, RJ Hayes, and Regind Happy lift the hog out of tub. New Zion, KY.
  - Splash, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0011)
    L-R Gary, Leroy Talbert, Amos Coma, RJ Hayes, and Regind Happy. The smell, the steam, and the heaviness in the air were so thick you could cut them with a knife. New Zion, KY.
  - Hog On Table, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0012)
    The hog has now been scalded in the hot tub of lye. This makes it easier to scrape the bristles off the hog. L-R Rodney Talbert, Amos Coma, RJ Hayes, Leroy Talbert. New Zion, KY.
  - Scraping Hog, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0013)
    RJ Hayes scraping off the bristles. Regind Happy next to him on right. New Zion, KY.
  - Getting Ready for Hook, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0014)
    Regind Happy and Gary Talbert have made a slit in the back of the legs near the tendon, which is how they will hang the hog. New Zion, KY.
  - Boot and Hog, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0015)
    Regind Happy putting in spool to hang hog. New Zion, KY.
  - Lifting Hog To Hang, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0016)
    RJ Hayes watches as Amos Coma takes the spool to lift the hog with Regind Happy helping him. New Zion, KY.
  - Hosing Hog, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0017)
    Derek Talbert hoses the hog. New Zion, KY.
  - Derek and Liver, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0018)
    Derek Talbert cleaning and saving liver. New Zion, KY.
  - 13 Hogs in 3 Hours, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0019)
    Derek Talbert sharpening knife. The group of men killed and cleaned 13 hogs in 3 hours. The men did this after they all had worked other jobs all day. New Zion, KY.
  - Uncle Joe and Hogs from the Night Before., 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0020)
    Uncle Joe bringing the hogs down to be butchered from the barn next door. New Zion, KY.
  - Butchering, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0021)
    The next morning it was the older men who came to do the butchering. I asked Uncle Ernest (back then I called him Mr. Talbert) why that was. "The younger ones don't have the interest to learn." L-R Eddie Moore, Fredrick Clay, Joe Mason and Ernest Talbert. New Zion, KY.
  - Sharpening Knives, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0022)
    L-R Joe Mason and Fredrick Clay sharpening knives. New Zion, KY.
  - Figgs Brothers, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0023)
    Johnny and Winston Figgs hanging out in what I called "The Club" behind Ernest Talbert's house. It is where they would meet, hang out, butcher the hogs, and maybe drink a bit. I asked Uncle Ernest once how many women had been in there and he saidŮ"well maybe Sarah Relford and you." I was honored. New Zion, KY.
  - Stirring Cracklins, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0024)
    Uncle Joe stirring cracklins. It took me a long time to learn Uncle Joe's last name. When I asked those who knew him really well they didn't know his last name either. Everyone just knew him as Uncle Joe. New Zion, KY.
  - Frying Pan, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0025)
    Johnny Figgs fries himself up some dinner in "the club." New Zion, KY.
  - Queenie, 2002 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0026)
    Queenie belonged to Uncle Ernest. He was the lead man and in charge of the hog killing and the butchering. It was his garage and his mother's barn where this was all done. Anyone who knew Ernest knew of his hams. He was famous for them. New Zion, KY.
  - Gene, Vehicles and Tobacco and, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0027)
    Gene Brown waiting for the rest of crew to plant. One thing about everyone in all of these communites is they always make sure to hire someone who needs work. Everyone always makes sure that everyone is taken care of. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Soon to be Tobacco Field, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0028)
    Dee Spencer driving the tobacco planter with Gene Brown on left and Lewis Burton on right. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Feeding the Planter, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0029)
    Gene Brown and Lewis Buron put the tobacco plants into the planter which will spit them out, plant them, and water them. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Ole Blue, 2001 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0030)
    Winston Figgs fixing his tractor. New Zion, KY.
  - Getting Ready To Plant, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0031)
    Lewis Burton, Gene Brown, and Dee Spencer. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Filling in the Gaps, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0032)
    Gene Brown fills in spots that the tobacco planter missed. Willa Lane, Ky.
  - Feet and Planter, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0033)
    The feet of Gene Brown and Lewis Burton and tobacco. Willa Lane, Ky.
  - Broken Tractor, 2001 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0034)
    Winston Figgs walks back to get tools to fix his tractor. New Zion, KY.
  - Lewis and Leaves, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0035)
    Lewis Burton chopping leaves in the fall. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Chopping Tobacco, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0036)
    Lewis Burton chopping tobacco. He came and did this after he finished his full-time job in Lexington. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Lewis, Rows and Van, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0037)
    Lewis Burton going down the rows chopping tobacco, his van in the back. Willa Lane, KY.
  - Winston Figgs and Tractor, 2001 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0038)
  - Lewis and Glasses, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0039)
    Lewis helping house tobacco. Uttingertown, KY.
  - NFL and Tobacco, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0040)
    Ronald Howard in the rafters housing tobacco. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Housing Tobacco, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0041)
  - Dee and Crew, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0042)
    Dee watches as Lewis Burton hands the tobacco to Gene Brown who passes it up to Ronald Howard. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Water and Stakes, 2003 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0043)
    Winston Figgs' Barn. New Zion, KY.
  - Cup, 2005 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0044)
    Ronald Howard after housing tobacco, always a hot job. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Tossing Tobacco, 2001 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0045)
    Winston Figgs in his barn tossing tobacco. He had told me the day before at church that he would be stripping tobacco in the barn the next day. I had been all over the barn, but never knew this room was there. In fact, I couldn't even find it until I heard Al Green coming from the portable radio. New Zion, KY.
  - Pulling Leaves/Stripping, 2001 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0046)
    Rosalynd Sydney Stripping tobacco in Winston Figgs' Barn. New Zion, KY.
  - Clarence Carrying, 2001 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0047)
    Clarence Thomas Chandler carrying stalks of tobacco which he will strip. Winston Figgs would go down to the Salvation Army and hire people who needed work. He would always pay them way more than minuim wage to try and help them. New Zion, KY.
  - Doug, 2004 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0048)
    Doug loading up Winston Figgs' truck to bring tobacco to the last live auction. Again, Winston Figgs helping someone who maybe needed help or work. What I know and knew of Doug was that he was a bit slow, his parents had died, and everybody kind of just made sure he was OK. Outside of Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Road to Last Live Tobacco Auction, 2004 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0049)
    Following Winston Figgs' truck. Fayette County, KY.
  - Tobacco Warehouse, 2004 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0050)
    There used to be rows and rows of them. Lexington, KY.
  - Last Live Auction, 2004 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0051)
    Winston Figgs looking at tobacco before the bidding. Lexington, KY.
  - The Office and Win, 2004 (Box 1, Print RL10153-P-0052)
    Winston Figgs sits in the office as they tell him they can't find his paperwork. As Duke has requested, I am trying to keep these captions short. This is a story I will write. All I can say is after the treatment of him this day I can't imagine back in the day. Lexington, KY.
  - Keene, 2000 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0053)
    Keene, Kentucky. The road hasn't changed much but the barns signs often do. Keene, KY.
  - Spring House, 2014 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0054)
    This is on Overbrook Farm, where Tom (Preston) Embry now lives. He is well into his 80s and always worked with the horses. I met him years ago. He is Clara Jackson's nephew and from the hamlets. He and his wife needed someplace to live and they let him live back here. There is always a spring house, deep in history and in this land. Overbrook Farm, KY.
  - Hunting Dogs, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0055)
    These dogs were behind Bunny Beatty's house in Fort Spring. I believe the dogs were rasied and sold by his grandson. The dogs, like Bunny, are long gone. I believe it was that grandson who built a pretty new house up the lane. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Basketball Hoop Pricetown, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0056)
    This is Macey Simpson's home in Pricetown. She invited us to her Labor Day party. She told the story of how they buried her old house. She now lives in a new trailer. Pricetown, KY.
  - Uttingertown Baptist Church Before Storm, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0057)
    Where all of the black residents of Uttingertown go as well as its town Columbustown. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Boydtown Bathroom, 2006 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0058)
    This at one time was a black hamlet. Now there is just one resident left, Miss Sally Mae Henderson. This was the old Methodist church which was closed and is now consolidated with New Zion. A Rosenwald school, now a home, stands next door. Boydtown, KY.
  - Hall, 2011 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0059)
    This is the old Hall church and outhouses. The church now empty. Hall was the hamlet right across the way from Camp Nelson. Hall, KY.
  - Plane Over Bethany Baptist, 2002 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0060)
    The Bluegrass Airport sits on the other side of Parkers Mill Road. Little Georgetown, KY.
  - Lawn Jockey, 2001 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0061)
    This jockey sat outside of Shelby Lee Miller's old home in Jimtown. Jimtown, KY.
  - The Elkhorn Creek, 2007 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0062)
    The Elkhorn Creek is just a mile shy of being called a river. It runs through many of the hamlets and has been used for everything, including baptisms. New Zion, KY.
  - Bracktown Jockey, 2011 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0063)
    The lawn jockey on Big Devil and Josephine Beatty's home. Bracktown, KY.
  - Jesus and Shelter, 2014 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0064)
    The cemetery behind New Vine Baptist Church. They got the seats from an old Greyhound bus station. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Jonestown Birdbath, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0065)
    There are two residents left in the old Jonestown as it was. This is in front of Rena Jeter's home. Jonestown, KY.
  - Ironing Curtains, 2009 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0066)
    The basement of Macedonia Baptist Church. They were getting ready for homecoming. Millville, KY.
  - Nylons, 2006 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0067)
    Mattie C's nylons drying on her front porch in Keene. Keene, KY.
  - Plane Over Little Georgetown, 2002 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0068)
    This was the last house on this side of Parkers Mill Road. It had a lot of dogs that all came out one night as I was about to shoot. All I saw were eyes. Little Georgetown, KY.
  - House of History, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0069)
    This was Biggerstaff's old house; it was built by her father. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Window View, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0070)
    Tom Harbut's front window with view of horse farm where he worked, as did his father. Groom to Man O War. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Dish and Slave Cabin, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0071)
    Bill Thomas brought me to this farm near Little Georgetown. His family were sharecroppers and lived next door. This was the old slave cabin. Fayette County, KY.
  - Classics, 2012 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0072)
    Old car and old barn, Zion Hill Days. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Sugarhill, 2006 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0073)
    Old cabin on Sugarhill, which was a vibrant hamlet. Only two residents left in 2006. Sugarhill, KY.
  - New Car New Zion, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0074)
    New car, New Zion. New Zion, KY.
  - Firmantown, 2014 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0075)
    Firmantown was a black hamlet. The last couple passed away right before I was supposed to have met them back 2002. New gate just went up separating from Firmantown. Firmantown, KY.
  - Pearidge, 2006 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0076)
    Pearidge was hit by a tornado years earlier, not much rebuilt. Pearidge, KY.
  - Tom's and Tobacco, 2001 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0077)
    Tom Harbut's house when his brother-in-law Gene Carter still grew tobacco. Mount Brillant farm. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Jimtown, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0078)
    View from inside Jimtown Baptist Church. Jimtown, KY.
  - Hootentown, 2006 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0079)
    The road to Hootentown. The church and I'm 99% sure an unidentified Rosenwald school. The church is still hanging on. Hootentown, KY.
  - Black Church White Church, 2005 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0080)
    This was the old Methodist church. The new white church was being built. It was flooding out and tearing up the graves of the old black hamlet. Cadentown, KY.
  - Jonestown, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0081)
    Most of the town, and as I was told, most of the cemetery was bulldozed to make way for condos. The church, two residents, and a barn were left in 2003. Jonestown, KY.
  - Cooley, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0082)
    Cooley Clay in paddock at Keeneland. Cooley knows EVERYONE! His brother Buck worked there as well. Buck played for the Kansas City Monarchs. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - Joe, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0083)
    Joe Edwards working in the winner's circle at Keeneland. He is one of the Jimtown Male Chorus members. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - Uncle Ernest, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0084)
    Ernest Talbert wasŮno words. He was my buddy. As I look at the captions so far and dates, I realize how much I stepped away from this work. Not much from 2008 as he died in Oct. 2007 and I struggeld as I missed him so. Here he is in the grandstand looking like he owned it. He worked in the paddock before he got sick then they moved him up here. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - The Crew, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0085)
    I can walk into Keeneland and run into someone from the hamlets, from the backside to the paddock up to the 4th floor bathrooms. Here are Joe Edwards Maurice?, Cooley Clay, and Bert Edwards. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - Bert, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0086)
    Bert Edwards looking over program. He is also a member of the Jimtown Male Chorus. This was turn-back-the-clock day, hence these hats. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - Bert in Paddock, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0087)
    Bert Edwards, one of the Jimtown Male Chorus, directing a horse in the paddock. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - Bert Ushering, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0088)
    Bert Edwards ushering people to their seats at Jimtown Baptist Church, kind of like ushering the horses in the Paddock. Keeneland Racetrack, Lexington, KY.
  - Ladies Day, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0089)
    Ladies day at Macedonia Baptist Church, all the ladies in white and being honored with a rose. Keene,KY.
  - Rev. Morton Boydtown, 2006 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0090)
    Rev. Lyle Morton at door of Boydtown Church where he was pastor until it closed and merged with New Zion. Boydtown, KY.
  - Welcome, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0091)
    Rhonda Turley ushers and opens church doors at Maddoxtown Baptisit Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Telling Secrets, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0092)
    Miss Martha Rankin whispering to Miss Eastrer. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Flatwoods, 2014 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0093)
    William Hunt front pew (one arm) and Barnell Hunt warming up to play for church. Flatwoods, KY.
  - Falling Out, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0094)
    This woman was feeling the spirit and is being fanned as the girls watch. Marble Creek, KY.
  - Come To Jesus, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0095)
    In Jimtown Baptist Church, a woman has come to take Jesus as she is comforted by one of the deacons, friends, and family. Jimtown, KY.
  - Rev.Harris, 2007 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0096)
    Rev. Harris steps in and preaches. Rev. Travis rests. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Sunday Deacons, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0097)
    Communion Sunday. The deacons prepare, Milwerd Gordon in front and Shorty lite in back. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Commuinion, 2001 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0098)
    Milwerd Gordon passes Communion to Lougenia Graves, Frances McDowell, and Teri Clay. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Jimtown Commuinion Sunday, 2004 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0099)
    Helen Warfield, communion Sunday. Jimtown, KY.
  - Miss Lenise, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0100)
    Lenise Beatty singing in the back. New Vine Baptist Church. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Making Change, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0101)
    The ushers making change for collection. Jimtown, KY.
  - Praise and Sleep, 2009 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0102)
    Praise and sleep. Maddoxtown, KY.